<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Schwitzd</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Schwitzd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.125.5</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:47:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Changelog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 15:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/changelog/</guid>
      <description>08.05.2024 Extendend the whoami page 05.05.2024 Initial website release with basic contents whoami, search and how I built this site. </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Not in My Picture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/not-in-my-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 11:39:18 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/not-in-my-picture/</guid>
      <description>Surely you have been in a situation where you wanted to wait before taking a photo because there were other people in the lens. Or think about how beautiful the photo of that square would have been without the people.
That&amp;rsquo;s it&amp;hellip; I do this almost every time I take a photo (apart from the time I was in the middle of nowhere in Iceland). So I said to myself: either I get up at 5am and take the photo, hoping that nobody else has had my bright idea, or we try to remove the objects with AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/architecture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 12:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/architecture/</guid>
      <description>This page provides a detailed overview of the architecture and implementation strategies behind my website. It delves into the fundamental principles guiding its design and development.
High-Level architecture My website is powered by Azure Static Web Apps, using the Hugo framework for its structure and functionality.
Architecture component list: Azure Static Web App Cloudflare Registrar Terraform GitHub Actions Deploying infrastructure Since I discovered Terraform (yes, I know IBM bought HashiCorp and now people are switching to OpenTofu) I have become a big fan of Infrastructure as Code.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How I Set Up This Site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-i-set-up-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2024 09:23:32 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-i-set-up-this-site/</guid>
      <description>While creating this blog, I thought why not write my first post documenting the steps I took to make it all happen? Maybe this could help other people who have decided to take the same journey as me, so let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Past experiences Actually this is my second blog, for several years I maintained a website called TuxLinux where I wrote about my first experiences in the Linux world, all using WordPress.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Whoami</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/whoami/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 20:21:16 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/whoami/</guid>
      <description>&amp;#x1f44b;, I&amp;rsquo;m Daniel and I&amp;rsquo;ve been in the IT world for as long as I can remember. I&amp;rsquo;m fascinated by all technology things, but my current passions lie in Security and DevOps.
I have been using Linux since back in 2003 when my father made me try SUSE Linux, from there I have tried them all. currently I use Arch Linux on my laptop and Debian on my Servers.
&amp;#x1f4d6; Much of my knowledge comes from people in the internet community who have decided to share their expertise freely.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
